{"data":[{"question":"When only a child my father took me to the circus.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"only","c":"my father took me","d":"the","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\nmy father took me -> my father would take me","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Going to the hill, we saw an old temple.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to","b":"the","c":"saw","d":"an","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- To-> down","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Between the communitarian philosophers, three of the most influential were Robert Owen, Charles Fourier, and John Humphrey Noyes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Between","b":"three","c":"influential","d":"and","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Between-> among","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Entering into the room, I found the light quite dazzling.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Entering","b":"into","c":"quite","d":"dazzling","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Into-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Mimosa Hotel is only 2 km from the most beautifully beaches.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Mimosa Hotel","b":"only 2 km","c":"from","d":"beautifully","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Beatufully-> beautiful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"After visiting the museum he had not very much time left.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"visiting","b":"had not","c":"very","d":"left","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Had not-> didn't have","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Before they had gone out they had been watching the news on T.V.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before","b":"had gone","c":"had been watching","d":"on","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Had gone-> went","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"She never wrote a letter by hand since she bought a word processor.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wrote","b":"by","c":"since","d":"bought","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Wrote-> has never written","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Please promise not telling anybody my secret.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"promise","b":"not","c":"telling","d":"anybody","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Telling-> to tell","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Maria had never complained about have a handicap.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"complained","c":"about","d":"have","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Have-> having","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}